this tutorial is about 45 degrees balls
本教程大约是45度球
所以这是一个例子，你用两块
this tutorial is about 45 degrees balls
so here's an example you use two pieces
分别是两个45度折叠
他们用来垂直举起一块
so here's an example you use two pieces
that are each two 45-degree folds and
蔓延中央脊柱上方
这里有一个例子
that are each two 45-degree folds and
they use to raise a piece vertically
马修·莱因哈特（Matthew Reinhart）和
在这种传播中，您可以在这里看到
they use to raise a piece vertically
above the central spine of the spread
这里有两个45度的折痕
用来举起中央支柱
above the central spine of the spread
there's an example here pop-up book of
支撑了这个平方传播
这实际上是在隐藏V形折叠
there's an example here pop-up book of
nursery rhymes by Matthew Reinhart and
在它下面，但要点是
教程是两个45度的人
nursery rhymes by Matthew Reinhart and
in this spread you can see here inside
还有另一个例子是
罗伯茨·奥布达的《绿野仙踪》
in this spread you can see here inside
here there are two 45-degree folds that
在最后的传播中，
看着它，举起宝座
here there are two 45-degree folds that
are used to raise the central pillar
下面有两个45度
折叠所以这是这个的主要用途
are used to raise the central pillar
that holds up this square spread and
这种机制，这是另一种方式
进行45度折叠
that holds up this square spread and
that's actually hiding a v-fold that's
教程11中的插槽需要两个
两张卡片都有折痕
that's actually hiding a v-fold that's
underneath it but the main point in this
沿着底部贴上标签
扭转他们这是经典
underneath it but the main point in this
tutorial is the two 45-degree folks
用您制作插槽的方式插槽，以便
这样放在一起然后切
tutorial is the two 45-degree folks
there's another example here this is The
到中间的两个杯子大约两个
毫米相距三毫米
there's another example here this is The
Wonderful Wizard of Oz by Roberts óbuda
分开
所以这两块很容易互锁
Wonderful Wizard of Oz by Roberts óbuda
and in the final spread the pillar that
这个可以粘在脊椎上
与脊椎齐平这会来
and in the final spread the pillar that
holds up the throne if you look at it
放在它上面并与它互锁
但是在我们这样做之前，我们需要添加
holds up the throne if you look at it
underneath here there are two 45-degree
45度折叠，所以45度折叠是
直角的地方非常容易
underneath here there are two 45-degree
folds so that's the main use of this
您只需将两个边缘对折即可
彼此然后一侧折痕
folds so that's the main use of this
this mechanism so this is another way of
真的很好，所以这里是折叠一个
45度折叠，然后将
this mechanism so this is another way of
making a 45-degree fold this is using
向上压线，那是
将直角一分为二
making a 45-degree fold this is using
slots which is in tutorial 11 take two
45度折痕有折痕
好，现在我们把这个放下来
slots which is in tutorial 11 take two
pieces of cards they both got a crease
与脊柱齐平，我就服用
这些这些角落在这里
pieces of cards they both got a crease
along the bottom a gluing tab put them
有一个另一件这些
会粘住两个水龙头
along the bottom a gluing tab put them
reverse them around this is classic
将以直角向下贴
脊椎可能会给它一些
reverse them around this is classic
slots the way you make slot so they're
平衡，所以您可以每种方式放一个
再次确保这些折痕是
slots the way you make slot so they're
put together like this and then you cut
真的很好剪掉角落
没有任何要塞的要点
put together like this and then you cut
up to the middle two cups about two
您可以将它们都放在
同时我把胶水放在两边
up to the middle two cups about two
millimeters apart three millimeters
因为他们将面对相反
指示涂抹胶水直到
millimeters apart three millimeters
apart
折痕
看起来不错，然后将其折叠
apart
so the two pieces will easily interlock
加冕以确保一切
工作舒适，所以有
this one can stick down to the spine
这是另一种方式，然后
建立了这个，你实际上可以采取
this one can stick down to the spine
flush with the spine this one will come
其他的东西，然后坚持下去
您可以开始构建某种
flush with the spine this one will come
down on top of it and interlock with it
树或花，或者你知道什么
想真正做到你可以坚持
down on top of it and interlock with it
but before we do that we need to add the
在这些上，您还得到了两个冲沟
你可以建立，所以我会
but before we do that we need to add the
45-degree folds so 45-degree fold is
贴上它们，直到关闭
这是一个封闭的沟壑
45-degree folds so 45-degree fold is
very easy where you've got a right angle
是一个即将关闭的沟渠
那些你可以添加反折条
very easy where you've got a right angle
you just fold the two edges up against
也是，所以我们拍一块像这样的折痕
折好一双折痕
you just fold the two edges up against
each other then one side crease it
进入它，因此在教程8中我们研究了
柜台折叠件，所以你可以
each other then one side crease it
really well so here are folding one
这样的小块，你可以
将它们粘在这两个沟渠中
really well so here are folding one
45-degree fold and then you fold the the
由主要机制创建，所以我将
只是坚持其中之一，然后任何
45-degree fold and then you fold the the
crease up against the line so that's
这些已经创建的飞机
你可以继续做那些
crease up against the line so that's
dividing the right angle into two
我将确保关闭
好吧，让我们稍微修剪一下
dividing the right angle into two
45-degree folds there it is crease it
在那里，你可以保持
在这些建筑物上添加额外的零件
45-degree folds there it is crease it
well and now we stick this one down
创造任何种类的雕塑
你有兴趣让你成为另一个
well and now we stick this one down
flush with the spine I'll just take
像这样的东西出现
飞机可以在上面展示
flush with the spine I'll just take
these these corners off here
你另一个例子，这是一条红色的风管
作者：大卫·卡特（David Carter），后面是
there's that one the other piece these
他是用这种技术把树做成的
如果你看这两个说法，这是
there's that one the other piece these
are going to stick down the two taps are
您可以看到这些机制是
这些侧面各45度折叠
are going to stick down the two taps are
going to stick down at right angles to
这两个其他的都进来了
不同的角度，使折痕产生
going to stick down at right angles to
the spine probably to give it some
经过调整，然后您还可以使用
对于这样的事情它正在使用
the spine probably to give it some
balance so you can put one each way
同样的想法，这是一座桥梁，所以这些
是它们的两个45度折痕
balance so you can put one each way
again I'll make sure these creases are
拉起你的整个机制
不得不反对
again I'll make sure these creases are
really good snip off the corners just so
彼此在这种情况下，您可以看到
你必须有一些平衡，所以
really good snip off the corners just so
there's no points that are going to snag
这个桥片的顶部是相同的
旋转器之间的长度
you can stick both these down at the
粘在另一边B是
相同的长度，所以你有
you can stick both these down at the
same time I put glue on opposite sides
平衡和我想做的最后一件事
告诉你这是一个正在使用
same time I put glue on opposite sides
as they're going to face in opposite
与我们在此处使用的相同技术
你有互锁的零件，但是
as they're going to face in opposite
directions smear the glue right up to
整个中间部分都被剪掉了
如果你看，我们又有了这条龙
directions smear the glue right up to
the crease
从上面直接看到
两只脚被压住了
looks about right and then just fold the
与脊柱平行
两只脚以90度角向下
looks about right and then just fold the
crown through to make sure it's all
脊柱，在每种情况下都有
这两条腿上的这些生物
crown through to make sure it's all
working comfortably so there it is
这些是45度的折痕，然后
这些头和尾巴是
working comfortably so there it is
that's another way of doing it and then
柜台里的折片看着
教程8，您可以找到一点点
that's another way of doing it and then
having built this you can actually take
关于45度折叠的更多信息
书籍弹出式设计和纸张力学
having built this you can actually take
other pieces and just stick them on so
您